ANISA BI. 132 FLAXLEY ROAD, STECHFORD, BIRMINGHAM B33 9HG.

TELEPHONE 07458366999. EMAIL ANISAB020@GMAIL.COM

EDUCATION

Sep 2012-July 2013: Central Campus - Sandwell College - NCFE Airline Cabin Crew

Sep 2011-July 2012: University College of Birmingham - Level 3 Travel and Tourism. Sep 2006-June 2011: Hodge Hill Girl's School Obtained 7 GCSE's, Grade C and above.

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A creative, enthusiastic and self-motivated individual with extensive work experience. Demonstrating excellent administration, communication and problem solving skills whilst being commercially minded. Offering a proven track record in the successful completion of tasks and meeting compliance procedures and deadlines.

WORK HISTORY

Galliford Try - Regional Administrator (6 month contract) - July 2019- Current

- Processing large amounts of invoices and creating purchase orders for subcontractors via Oracle.
- Liaising with Facilities Managers when processing invoices ensuring they are approved and signed for.
- Inputting timesheets weekly for laborer's.
- Welcoming visitors for meetings and directing accordingly.
- Once jobs are completed updating systems and spreadsheets.
- Handling 5 site contracts for e.g Birmingham City University and various school sites dealing with financial queries and any jobs to be raised/completed.
- Chasing subcontractors for outstanding quotes and invoices.
- Inspect sites for any hazards and report if necessary.
- Keeping all files and folders updated and in order.
- · Providing administrative cover for absent staff.
- Ordering any office stationery/materials for direct staff.

MITIE- Administrator (Temporary) - May 2019-June 2019

- Completing general admin duties scanning, filing and photocopying job sheets.
- Booking in PPM jobs for major retail stores fire alarm checks and sprinkler flow tests.
- Coding engineers timesheets.
- Updating jobs on the system MAXIMO.
- Working from numerous spreadsheets to ensure all tasks are completed.
- Handling Team Managers diary booking in meetings.
- Providing help to colleagues with moving to a newer office ensuring all important documents were stored away correctly.
- Answering calls from clients and engineers.

Dodd Group – Solihull Community Housing – Administrator/Scheduler (Maternity Cover) – May 2018 – March 2019

- Maintaining information on gas servicing, repairs & installations in line with legal requirements.
- Taking high volume of calls from tenants wanting to book/rearrange their appointments.
- Arranging over 200 letters to be posted out weekly to chase tenants who have not responded.

- Scheduling engineers workloads ensuring all jobs are handed out before the next day.
- Producing excel spreadsheets to keep up to date with any gas certificates that have been received.
- Scanning and printing a large number of documents to then upload into allocated databases.
- Coding engineers timesheets to ensure their wages are paid correctly and our job costs are accurate.
- Greeting visitors to the office and providing refreshments.

Messenger Building, Conserving & Repairing LTD – Administrator- November 2016 – April 2018

- Creating, filing and updating new and existing insurance claims on various websites and systems.
- Dealing with Accounts queries issuing PO's and submitting invoices.
- Administrational assistance to Regional Manager & Contract Manager for e.g. diary managing, note taking, and meeting arrangements.
- Updating timesheets weekly for labour workers and agency staff.
- Scheduling site visits between Contract Managers and second party insurance companies.
- Communicating with debtors to chase outstanding payments.
- Ensuring information is updated regarding each job on numerous websites used.
- Ordering items such as skips, paint etc for each job accordingly.
- Ensuring all inquiries are answered via phone/email/letters.
- Managing office site whilst Contract Manager is away on site.

UNITE Student Accommodation - Service & Sales Advisor - May 2016- September 2016

- Welcoming visitors and contractors on to the property issuing visitor passes.
- Checking students in and out the accommodation.
- Managing keys for colleagues and lock outs.
- Logging required maintenance within the properties ensuring it has been completed successfully.
- Processing student's bookings and payments.
- Aiding with financial administration.
- Creating daily debt/sales report using Microsoft Excel and Oracle.
- Chasing outstanding debt from students.
- Performing communal and room inspections following company procedures.
- Maintaining a clean and safe environment for fellow students and colleagues.

BMG Research Agency - Quantitative & Qualitative Telephone Interviewer - December 2014 - November 2015

- Achieving daily targets of completed surveys via telephone successfully.
- Asking questions in accordance with instructions to obtain various specified information required.
- Explain survey objectives and procedures to interviewees.
- Interpret survey questions to help interviewees' comprehension.
- Correcting interviewee's details if incorrect.
- Resolving and identifying inconsistencies in interviewees' responses by means of appropriate questioning.
- Reviewing data obtained from interviews for completeness and accuracy.

UNITE Student Accommodation - Customer Service/Administrative Assistant - August 2014 (Temporary, 6 Weeks)

- Maintaining UNITE's information systems including booking system, hardcopy files and Excel spreadsheets ensuring customer data is accurate and secure.
- Filing, compiling check-in packs, delivering documents to rooms.
- Creating key-cards for the customer's rooms using a programme called 'Ving'.
- Answering telephone queries and providing effective customer service.

- Meet and Greet for customers.
- Customer orientation and escorting customers to their rooms.
- Assisting customers in a professional and courteous manner, showing empathy and responding with urgency to queries.

CAPGEMINI - Front of House Receptionist/ Facilities Assistant - July 2014 (Temporary, 2 Weeks)

- Taking calls for room bookings.
- Booking and cancelling rooms for clients.
- Responding to emails.
- Logging queries and problems into the helpdesk system.
- Preparing refreshments for clients.
- Desk utilisation.
- Checking meeting rooms prior and after use.
- Collecting and escalating daily post and packages.
- Updating and creating spreadsheets.
- Making sure equipment is ready for use in meeting or vc rooms.
- Taking minutes during meetings.

Eyeworld Opticians - Receptionist/Admin Assistant - December 2012 - February 2013

- Meeting and greeting patients on a daily basis.
- Typing documents and distributing memos.
- Handling incoming/outgoing calls.
- Correspondence and filing.
- Faxing, printing, photocopying and scanning medical records.
- Monitoring inventory, office stock and ordering supplies as necessary.
- General knowledge of products and advising customers of what would suit them best.
- Processing orders and informing patients once orders have arrived.

HOBBIES

Baking - Thoroughly enjoy discovering new recipes to bake on the weekends with family.

Reading - Prefer novels – favorite author is Paulo Coelho.

Tennis - Love keeping active with a great fun activity.

Socializing - From shopping to dining out and watching movies with my friends.

Travel - Travelled extensively through Europe visited places which include Turkey, France, Germany, Portugal and Spain.

SKILLS

Computing skills - Easily adapt to different programmes/softwares.

Teamwork- Work confidently within a group.

Verbal/Written Communication - Able to express myself clearly in writing/speaking in a high standard of English.

Planning & Organizing - Able to prioritize tasks and see them through to completion.

References available upon request.